Alaw Moradi

alaw.m@hotmail.com 0401 237 706

Personal profile

My name is Alaw, graduated teacher from Stockholm, Sweden based in Sydney. Past experiences in different environments and jobs has given me the ability to easily adapt and learn, while enjoying working in teams and meeting new people.

Education

Gothenburg University

2015-2018, Gothenburg
Degree of Bachelor of Arts in Primary
Education – Extended School, Home
Economics and Swedish

JENSEN High School

2010-2013, Stockholm Studies of social science

Languages

Swedish - Moder tounge Kurdish - Moder tounge English - Fluency in both written and spoken

Other skills

Working With Children's Check CPR Certified RSA Certificate

Work experience

Octopus Retail P/L

2020, Sydney Retail assistant

Beach Road Hotel

2019, Sydney Bartender

Bowls Club

2019, Innisfail
Bar work, functions, glassie

Thinque

2019, Sydney Nanny

Happy Ears

2016-2018, Gothenburg Seller, promoter

White and White

2016-2018, Gothenburg Seller, promoter, event planner

Österödskolan (Primary School)

2015-2018 Gothenburg Primary School Teacher

Trulsegardsskolan (Torslanda Secondary School)

2017, Gothenburg Home Economics Teacher

Skolverket conferens (Reachem)

2016-2017, Gothenburg Receptionist